(dramatic orchestral music)
(singing)
When seasons come, our hearts
will bloom. Every petal within shines
bright and true. Plenty
will flourish, deep in our hearts.
We will bear the mark of roses
of Rome. (echoes)
Roses of Rome, let us bloom
forever. Roses of Rome, may we
always be with you, ever. Though
time may fade the colors we
wear, our roots stand firm where
glory finds its home. Through
every tear joined and whispered
prayer, we still remain the roses
of Rome. (echoes)
Roses of Rome. (echoes)
Roses of Rome, let us bloom
forever. Roses of Rome, may we
always be with you, ever.
Though time may fade the colors we wear,
our roots stand firm where glory finds its
home.
Through every tear joined and whispered
prayer, we still remain the roses
of Rome. (echoes)
Roses of Rome, let us bloom
forever. Roses of Rome,
may we always be with you, ever.
So when we part, let memories sing.
A love immortal, carved in stone.
With every breath and every spring,
we still remain the roses of Rome.
(song ends)